

# PORTFOLIO CO

## **Personal Info**

Jalan Gombak, Kuala Lumpur, 53100, Malaysia 01123270509 safi@angeyza.com

### Links

Article website
Setia Awan
Admin Site
Sports Information

## Skills

JavaScript

**CSS** 

**HTML** 

MySQL

NodeJs

Angular

MongoDB

Git

Responsive Design

Teamwork

Problem-solving

# Languages

**Pashto** 

English

# Qandagha Safi

Web Developer



As a team-oriented and skilled Computer Science graduate with over 4 years of progressive experience in software engineering and web development, I am eager to seek a challenging position in your esteemed organization. As an Afghan national who has studied and worked in Malaysia, I am available to start working immediately.

## **Work Experience**

#### Web developer, MYCN Sdn Bhd, Kuala Lumpur

June 2019 - Present

I have been working on a large and complex project. My key responsibilities and achievements include:

- Writing reusable and clean programing code to develop 12/18 web and backend services.
- Working on frontend and backend using Nodejs, Angular, Mongodb, Redis, Zookeeper

Software engineer and web developer, Tektician (Part-Time), Perak January 2019 - June 2019

My main responsibilities and achievements include:

- Enhancing customizing ERPnext components
- Writing clean frontend and backend code for features.

#### Education

#### Bacheloar's OF Computer Science, IIUM (3.65)

August 2014 - February 2019

#### Courses

#### Become a Full-Stack Web Developer, LinkedIn

January 2023 - February 2023

Career Essentials in Software Development by Microsoft and LinkedIn, Microsoft

January 2023 - February 2023

#### References

jonathan@tektician.com

hgun77@gmail.com